Hello!

I'm Shelby Courtney

I'm a Junior Web Developer, trained in Front End Development and currently learning Python. I come from a rich Customer Service background with over 10 years in management roles for high volume and high traffic retail stores, and over 6 years in Interior Design. I believe software should be beautiful to look at and easy to use from all experience levels.



CONTACT ✓ shelbycodes@gmail.com **§** 281.630.9470 ☐ https://shelbycodes.me

Work Experience:

2016 - Present | Pottery Barn

Associate Store Manager - This role oversees sales and operations management, merchandising, and displays of a \$14M retail store.

2019 - Present | Modsy

Remote Interior Designer - This role works one-onone with customers, creating a design vision and producing it into a 3D realization.

2014 - 2016 | Anthropologie

Selling Department Manager - This role ran the sales team, hiring, and training for a \$9M retail store.

Education & Courses:

SheCodes

April 2022

Certified in Front End Development

May 2022

Certified in Responsive Web Development

June 2022

Certified in React Development

BA - Fashion Merchandising

November 2014
International Academy of Design & Technology

Currently Studying: Python

Technical Skills:









